# Kazi Ifrat Sultana

## Frontend Developer

↑ Khilkhet, Dhaka-1229 | \$\square\$ +8801831305640 | \$\square\$ ifratbinte@gmail.com



## **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

To obtain the position of Interactive & Creative Frontend Developer with a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 3+ years' experience in development. Pursuing a role as a frontend developer with a passion for creating immersive user experiences. Ability to work in any environment and possesses good analytical skills.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### JUN, 2022 - CURRENT

#### **React Developer/Bdtask Limited**

- Working on Trading Stock Market Broker House
- Developed Stock Market Web Application
- Structured, developed different web-based applications using Vite, Typescript, Rest API, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind & Bootstrap

#### FEB, 2021 - APR, 2022

#### Frontend Developer/Softnio

- Developed Multipurpose Admin Panel theme using Bootstrap, dart-sass & Gulp.js.
- Worked on conceptual apps PMS, CMS, LMS, CRM, HMS, HRM & Investment panel.
- Worked on Cryptocurrency Theme.
- Worked with Theme mode and RTL. Having sound experience in Themeforest theme development.

#### NOV, 2020 - JAN, 2021

#### Frontend Developer/Planet Hack Limited

- Worked Admin Panel theme & E-commerce User Interface using Bootstrap & SASS.
- Developed beauty hacks conceptual app Purler Management System.

## **PROJECTS**

• Stackhouse: 157.245.56.86:3000

Technologies: Typescript, Rest API, Web Socket, Redux

• **Metal Advance**: github.com/lfratbinte/Metal Advance

Technologies: Typescript, Rest API, Redux Toolkit, Bootstrap, Vite.

Benemoy Securities Limited : benemoysecurities.com

Technologies: Typescript, Rest API, Redux, Vite

Midway Ecommerce : github.com/Ifratbinte/midway ecommerce

Technologies: React.js, Bootstrap, SASS, Flex

### **SKILLS**

- **Specialization:** TypeScript, React, Rest API, Redux Toolkit, Tailwind, Material UI, Base build with html5, Bootstrap, SASS, Flex, Animation.
- Tools: Git, Taiga, Jira, Gulp, Vite.
- Quite knowledge in web socket protocol.

## **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2020

## **BSc. in Computer Science & Engineering**

Britannia University CGPA – 3.54

2013 - 2014

## **Higher Secondary School Certificate**

Chandina Women's College GPA – 4.75

2011 - 2012

## **Secondary School Certificate**

Chandina Dr. Firoza Pilot Girls High School GPA – 5.00

## LANGUAGE PROFICENCY

Fluent in speaking in Bengali, English. Reading and writing both in English and Bengali.

### **DECLARATION**

I hereby solemnly declare that all the above statement is true, currently to the best of knowledge and belief.

#### **Kazi Ifrat Sultana**